GAURAV DIPAK TAMBATKAR (1) Featured

Senior Software Engineer, Seeking assignments in Software Development, Application Programming, Program Management, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, C, Java, RestFul API, Html5, Css, JavaScript, JSON, Angular, Node js, Typescript, Photoshop



Current Designation: Senior Software Engineer Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)

Current Company: Birlasoft Limited Notice Period: 3 Months

Current Location: Mumbai Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Mumbai, Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: software developer, application programming, program management, requirement gathering, system

analysis,restful api,angular,node js,mysql,photoshop,bootstrap,Ajax,Javascript,senior software

engineer, Java, JQuery, HTML, JSON, html5, CSS, Software Development

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 13-Jan-21 Last Modified: 13-Jan-21

Summary

Senior Software Engineer with 2+ years of work exposure in Software Development, Application Programming, Program Management, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, C, Java, RestFul API, Html5, Css, JavaScript, JSON, Angular, Node js, Oracle, Eclipse.

Work Experience

Birlasoft Limited as Senior Software Engineer

Oct 2020 to Till Date

Information Gathering, Creating Wireframe, design and implement and scripting.

Carufus Technology Pvt Ltd as Senior Software Engineer

Apr 2018 to Sep 2020

The Unique Media Solution as Software Developer

Jul 2016 to Apr 2018

Creating responsive user-interface using HTML5 and CSS, SASS, Bootstrap.

Calling API and manipulation of data over multiple webpages. Storing JSON responses and show it on frond -end as per client's requirements.

Make application/software more functional/responsive by Angular JavaScript (MVC Implementation).

Create various kind of API using java in jersey framework (Restful API).

Write multiple SQL queries to get and set data. Handle it to create different kinds of API.

Have worked on Android xml designing and activity creation too.

Convert PSD files into HTML.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from University of Mumbai in 2016

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Windows 7 / 8/10/Linux	
C,Java,RestFul API, Html5,Css3	
JavaScript,JSON,Angular, Node js	
Oracle 10g / 11g	
IntelliJ IDEA, Eclipse, Visual Studio	
FileZilla, HeidiSQL, Photoshop	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Hindi	Proficient			
Marathi	Expert			

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time